Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives and Contact Sheets
  - U-M Men's Basketball photos
    - 1978-1979
      - Illinois 2/03/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Northwestern 2/15/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Wisconsin 2/22/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Purdue 2/24/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
    - 1979-1980
      - Windsor 11/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Massachusetts 12/01/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Central Michigan 12/03/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Detroit 12/12/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Dayton 12/15/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Western Michigan 12/22/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 17)
      - Minnesota 1/03/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Iowa 1/05/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Ohio State 1/19/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Michigan State 1/24/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Northwestern 2/02/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Illinois 2/14/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Purdue 2/21/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Indiana 2/23/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Nebraska 3/06/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Texas-El Paso 3/11/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
    - 1980-1981
      - Eastern Michigan 11/29/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Arkansas 12/06/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Akron 12/08/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Kent State 12/10/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Western Michigan 12/20/1980, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Indiana 1/15/1981, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Iowa 1/17/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Illinois 1/22/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Ohio State 2/12/1981, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Michigan State 2/14/1981, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Northwestern 2/21/1981, negatives, contact sheets, slides (Box 18)
      - Basketball banquet 3/02/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Minnesota 3/05/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Purdue 3/07/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Duquesne 3/12/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
      - Toledo 3/15/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 18)
    - 1981-1982
      - Eastern Michigan 11/30/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Northern Michigan 12/07/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Detroit 12/19/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Louisiana Tech 12/21/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Wisconsin 1/07/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Purdue 1/09/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Michigan State 1/21/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Ohio State 1/28/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Illinois 2/06/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Minnesota 2/11/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Northwestern 2/13/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Iowa 2/20/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Indiana 2/27/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
    - 1982-1983
      - Freshman recruits 7/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Windsor 11/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Akron 11/27/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Northern Michigan 12/04/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Kansas 12/06/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Cleveland State 12/08/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Florida A&M 12/27/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Pennsylvania 12/30/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Minnesota 1/12/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Wisconsin 1/15/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Purdue 1/27/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Illinois 1/29/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Michigan State 2/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Indiana 2/24/1983, photos, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Ohio State 2/26/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Iowa 3/10/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Northwestern 3/12/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
    - 1983-1984
      - North Carolina A&T 11/28/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Central Michigan 11/30/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Northern Michigan 12/03/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 19)
      - Dayton 12/10/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Northwestern 1/05/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Iowa 1/07/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Ohio State 1/19/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Indiana 1/21/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Illinois 2/16/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Purdue 2/18/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Wisconsin 3/01/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Minnesota 3/03/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Wichita State 3/15/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Marquette 3/19/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Xavier 3/22/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
    - 1984-1985
      - Yugoslavia 11/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Georgia 12/01/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Youngstown State 12/05/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Western Michigan 12/10/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/12/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Alcorn State 12/17/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Rutgers 12/22/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Indiana 1/02/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Minnesota 1/17/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Iowa 1/19/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Michigan State 1/24/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Kansas 1/27/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Purdue 2/07/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Illinois 2/09/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
    - 1985-1986
      - Tennessee 12/02/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Youngstown State 12/04/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Florida Southern 12/07/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Chicago State 12/09/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Central Michigan 12/12/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Western Michigan 12/14/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Northern Michigan 12/21/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Cleveland State 12/29/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 20)
      - Illinois 1/08/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Purdue 1/11/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Northwestern 1/30/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Wisconsin 2/01/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Minnesota 2/13/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Michigan State 2/20/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Indiana 3/08/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
    - 1986-1987
      - Ball State 12/01/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Central Michigan 12/03/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Illinois-Chicago 12/06/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Kent State 12/09/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Northern Michigan 12/20/1986, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Ohio State 1/08/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Indiana 1/12/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Michigan State 1/15/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Syracuse 1/18/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Minnesota 1/29/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Northwestern 2/21/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Iowa 2/28/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Illinois 3/04/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Purdue 3/07/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
    - 1987-1988
      - Bowling Green 12/02/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Central Michigan 12/04/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Austin Peay 12/10/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/12/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Grambling 12/21/1987, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Minnesota 1/09/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Illinois 1/28/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Iowa 2/03/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Purdue 2/07/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Indiana 2/13/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Northwestern 3/02/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
      - Ohio State 3/12/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 21)
    - 1988-1989
      - Yugoslavia 11/16/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - South Dakota State 12/03/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/12/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Northern Michigan 12/20/1988, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Northwestern 1/07/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Minnesota 1/12/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Indiana 1/23/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Michigan State 2/04/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Wisconsin 2/25/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Iowa 3/04/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Illinois 3/11/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
    - 1989-1990
      - Poland 11/14/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Grambling 11/29/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Iowa State 12/02/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Duke 12/09/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Northern Michigan 12/28/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/30/1989, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Minnesota 1/13/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Ohio State 1/19/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Michigan State 1/27/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Purdue 1/31/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Indiana 2/08/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Illinois 2/11/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Wisconsin 3/08/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Iowa 3/10/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
    - 1990-1991
      - Central Michigan 11/28/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Utah 12/01/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/04/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Chicago State 12/12/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Marquette 12/22/1990, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Ohio State 1/05/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Northwestern 1/17/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Indiana 1/24/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Iowa 2/09/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Wisconsin 2/21/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Minnesota 3/03/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
      - Michigan State 3/09/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 22)
    - 1991-1992
      - Cuba 11/14/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Chicago State 12/09/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/12/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Duke 12/14/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Central Michigan 12/15/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Rice 12/21/1991, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Purdue 1/15/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Ohio State 2/02/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Northwestern 2/05/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Minnesota 2/19/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Indiana 3/08/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Illinois 3/14/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
    - 1992-1993
      - Ragnon 11/23/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Detroit Titans 12/07/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Cleveland State 12/14/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Central Michigan 12/21/1992, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Indiana 1/12/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Ohio State 1/26/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Purdue 2/07/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Minnesota 2/20/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Iowa 3/02/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Michigan State 3/07/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
    - 1993-1994
      - Croatia 11/16/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Ragnon 11/22/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Cleveland State 11/29/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Tennessee-Chattanooga 12/04/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Duke 12/11/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Central Michigan 12/20/1993, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Michigan State 1/05/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Ohio State 1/13/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Wisconsin 1/29/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Boston University 1/03/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
      - Indiana 2/08/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 23)
    - 1994-1995
      - Poland 11/16/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - High five 11/28/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Detroit 12/05/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Pennsylvania 12/13/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Jackson State 12/22/1994, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Purdue 1/03/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Iowa 1/11/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Michigan State 1/22/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - St. John's 1/29/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Wisconsin 2/01/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Ohio State 2/08/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Indiana 2/19/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Northwestern 3/01/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Penn State 3/08/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
    - 1995-1996
      - AIA 11/01/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Russia 11/09/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - DePaul 11/15/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Weber St. 11/17/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - St. Francis 11/27/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Duke 12/09/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Washington 12/16/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Cleveland State 12/18/1995, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Northwestern 1/06/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Illinois 1/09/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Penn State 1/21/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Purdue 1/31/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Iowa 2/13/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Indiana 2/18/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Minnesota 2/24/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Michigan State 2/27/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Wisconsin 3/09/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
    - 1996-1997
      - Australia 11/11/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - AIA 11/18/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Ball State 11/26/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 24)
      - Bradley 12/02/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Detroit 12/05/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Arizona 12/21/1996, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Ohio State 1/02/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Illinois 1/09/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Purdue 1/16/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Iowa 1/19/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Michigan State 2/01/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Penn State 2/08/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Indiana 2/16/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Minnesota 2/26/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Northwestern 3/05/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Miami (FL) 3/13/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Oklahoma State 3/18/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
    - 1997-1998
      - AIA 11/03/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Russia 11/10/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Western Michigan 11/15/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Cleveland State 11/19/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Florida International 12/03/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Nevada-Las Vegas 12/06/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Eastern Michigan 12/17/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Duke 12/13/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Tennessee-Chattanooga 12/20/1997, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Penn State 1/03/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Michigan State 1/10/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Minnesota 1/20/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Purdue 1/29/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Northwestern 2/05/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Ohio State 2/11/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Indiana 2/22/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
      - Wisconsin 2/28/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 25)
    - 1998-1999
      - AIA 11/09/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Ball State 11/16/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Detroit 11/19/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Towson 11/30/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Bradley 12/02/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Hampton 12/21/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Wisconsin 12/30/1998, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Indiana 1/05/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Ohio State 1/16/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Illinois 1/28/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Iowa 1/30/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Minnesota 2/07/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Michigan State 2/18/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Penn State 2/24/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
    - 1999-2000
      - Media Day 10/13/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Scrimmage 11/06/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - California All-Stars 11/10/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Prestige 11/14/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Oakland 11/19/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Oakland 11/19/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Detroit 11/23/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Western Michigan 11/27/1999, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Western Michigan 11/27/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Tennessee-Chattanooga 12/04/1999, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Michigan State 2/01/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Ohio State 2/06/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Indiana 2/13/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Penn State 2/19/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Purdue 2/24/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Iowa 3/02/2000, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
    - 2000-2001
      - Western Michigan,11/21/2000, negatives (Box 26)
      - Wagner 11/25/2000, negatives (Box 26)
      - Wake Forest 11/28/2000, negatives (Box 26)
      - Bowling Green 12/13/2000, negatives (Box 26)
      - Towson State 12/27/2000, negatives (Box 26)
  - U-M Baseball photos
    - 1975
      - Minnesota 4/1975, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
    - 1976
      - Toledo 4/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Michigan State 5/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Ohio State (and Track, Ann Arbor Federation Meet) 5/1976, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
    - 1977
      - Minnesota 4/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Michigan State 5/1977, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
    - 1978
      - Illinois 4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Purdue 4/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
      - Ohio State 5/1978, negatives, contact sheets (Box 26)
    - 1979
      - Iowa 5/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Northwestern 5/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Western Michigan 5/1979, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1980
      - Central Michigan 4/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Michigan State 4/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Central Michigan 5/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Ohio State 5/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Purdue & Illinois 5/1980, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1981
      - Cleveland State 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Detroit 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Indiana 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Western Michigan 4/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Illinois 5/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Minnesota 5/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Purdue 5/1981, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1982
      - Grand Valley State 3/1982 (Box 27)
      - Cleveland State 4/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Toledo 4/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Western Michigan 4/1982 (Box 27)
      - 5/02/1982, negatives (Box 27)
      - Adrian 5/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Michigan State 5/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Wayne State 5/1982, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1983
      - Aquinas 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Cleveland State 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Indiana 4/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Adrian 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Iowa 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Minnesota 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Purdue 5/1983, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1984
      - Grand Valley State 3/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Eastern Michigan 4/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Ohio State 4/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Michigan State 5/1984, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1985
      - Bowling Green 4/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Indiana 4/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Siena Heights 4/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Eastern Michigan 5/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Ferris State 5/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Michigan State 5/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
      - Purdue 5/1985, negatives, contact sheets (Box 27)
    - 1986